Yeah, this is just downright evil. A French streamer named Jean Parmanov, real name Raphael Graven,
has passed away in his sleep on stream after this marathon stream that he was a part of,
where his friends, and I wouldn't call them friends there, like actual demons,
basically just abused him, beat him, fundamentally tortured him, made him consume dangerous things,
and then he went to sleep and died in his sleep. He was 46 years old, and the exact cause of death
is currently being investigated. Jean Parmanov was mainly a gamer, and then over time
grew a big following and started doing like more IRL streams, and from what I can
gather, more like extreme challenges. But what happened during this marathon stream, where he
ultimately passed away, was something that he was not a full willing participant of, as evidence
by what he would say during streams, as well as a text message he sent to his mother just days
before his death. He allegedly sent this to his mom shortly before he passed, hey mom, how are you?
I'm sick of this game, it's gone way too far, I feel like I'm being held hostage by their awful
concept, I'm exhausted, I want to leave, but the other guy won't let me, he's holding me hostage.
The other streamers involved here are trying to claim they had nothing to do with it, and then
even posted some very heartfelt messages about his passing and how much he meant to them.
But if you watch any of the footage, and I don't know what I can and can't show you here,
because it is actually torturing this guy, and then he eventually dies,
if you just watch that, it's very clear, this isn't a man they respected, this is someone they
treated like a human punching bag.
I've seen a few new sources showing these clips, so I'm assuming that these are okay to show,
not that any of it is okay, it only gets worse from here, but as far as what they did to this man
and the abuse that he endured, this is like the lowest level of it, not that there's a such thing
as diet torture, there's no such thing as like a tasteful amount of torture, but as far as like
what to show, it is shocking that it went on for so long. Like this was not just like a one-time
thing, this was a recurrent gag on their streams where they bring Jon in, and then they all just
turn into like the toddlers from weapons and start like ripping at him, beating him, insulting him,
they really treat him like their prisoner, like a dog's chew toy or something, it is foul,
and they have the audacity to claim that they did nothing and that they are blameless in this death,
like oh it was just such an unexpected tragedy that he passed away, no one could have seen it coming.
I think any sensible person will look at all of the evidence that they themselves filmed on stream,
and be able to say with high level of confidence that they definitely had a hand in his untimely death.
Two of the streamers directly involved in this have made statements where they're trying to put
on this façade of grief, but I don't buy it at all. The first comes from Naruto, which is a wild
name for a piece of shit like this to have, it's been a while since I've seen the show, but I don't
recall Naruto ever being a huge advocate for torturing innocent people. Anyway, a statement says,
I've always dreaded writing these words, sadly last night J.P. Raphael Graven left us, my brother,
my sidekick, my partner, six years side by side, never letting go. I love you my brother,
we will miss you terribly, please respect his memory and don't share the video of his final moments,
for his family and for us, his second family, rest in peace. A bunch of words there, and I don't
believe any of them. All of these words are once again more meaningless than Mahuja Nais, and that's
a word that I completely made up. This is hollow when you look at how they treated this guy for so long.
It wasn't just the physical abuse that J.P. Raphael Graven endured. It was the mental abuse,
they would all, like from what I can tell, they were even doing their best to keep him from sleeping,
they were strangling him as well, which of course is physical too, but there was significantly more
than just the physical stuff they were doing to him to mistreat him and abuse him and dehumanize him.
It was terrible, it was truly terrible. Obviously, I'm not going to show any more from the stream,
but do you want to know how they went to check if he was still alive? Well, when they thought
something might be a bit awry, they threw a bottle at him. They just threw a bottle at his body,
and then they went over and started slapping him to try and see if he'd wake up, but he was still
unresponsive. So that's when it dawned on them that he had died in his sleep on stream, right next
to all of them. There is nothing that I have seen here that leads me to believe they genuinely cared
about this guy. I think it's very clear Rafael Groven very much cared about them and wanted to
be their friend, and to me it seems like they exploited that. They manipulated him into being
the butt of the joke for these humiliation streams. That's what these were. They were humiliation
streams that they roped Rafael Groven into agreeing to, and it seems like they were just dangling
this carrot of friendship in front of him, and all of the attention that it was gathering,
it seems like they were holding over his head like, oh man, we need you here, JP, we need to
you know mistreat you on stream, but just know we love you. This is all part of the joke here
for the audience. We're all in on it. We're not laughing at you. We're laughing with you.
That's when it seems like to me from everything I have seen here, and this has gone on for a really
long time. It really seems like at no point did they actually respect JP or treat him like a friend.
He was simply the catalyst for their humiliation streams, because of him they were able to get a lot
more eyeballs and make a lot more money off humiliating and abusing this guy that they never
actually really viewed as a friend. That's what it looks like to me. Now all of this was broadcast
on kick, and it went on for a long time. Not only this 10-day marathon, but a lot of the other
abuse that happened prior also broadcast on kick, and at no point were they ever like reprimanded or
shut down according to sources, so a lot of attention is now turning towards kick about like how
they handle illegal shit like this. So our priority is to protect creators and ensure a safer
environment on kick. All co-streamers who participated in this live broadcast have been banned pending
the ongoing investigation, so they didn't ban until after JP's death. Now this kind of thing has
happened on Twitch before. This isn't exclusive to just kick. This has happened on YouTube streaming
before as well. There was a streamer a while back on YouTube who literally murdered his girlfriend
on stream. This is unfortunately something that has happened on other streaming platforms,
and I understand that it can oftentimes be hard for a company to proactively get involved and
stop something from happening before it happens, preventing a tragedy. This isn't fucking minority
report here with Tom Cruise able to like see the future or some shit. They couldn't prevent it in
some of those cases, but this one's a little different because a big source of their content was
mistreating JP on stream, strangling him, beating him. That was a big piece of their content for
a while even before all of this blew up and he passed away. I feel like at some point, kick could
have absolutely been alerted to that and taken action. And kick does have a history of letting
criminal activity fly unpunished for a while. There is a streamer that I have talked about numerous
times who has literally fucked a prostitute on stream on kick in front of a child on stream and
still was never banned for that. And that wasn't even the first time that he fucked a prostitute on
stream, but that was the first time he did that while a child was literally in the room while he
had sex with that prostitute. Still, never banned. Kick has been very Lucy Goosey with their
enforcement of their own policies where they will let criminal activity fly for way too long.
So that is something I think they really need to get under control. Kick has been growing a lot
recently and I think if it wants to continue to grow, it needs to take shit like this far more
seriously. Like before something like this happens, I feel like day one of JP being abused during
this 10 day marathon kick could have come in and just put the kibbash on it. I'm not saying that
would have saved his life or anything like that. Of course, there's no way to know. But if kick
would just be a little more mindful of trying to prevent illegal activities from being broadcast on
there, it'd be really helpful not only to the platform, but to people like JP, where if his
friends weren't receiving such monetary incentive to keep humiliating and abusing him,
like if they had been banned by kick, well maybe they would have stopped. But when they get to do an
entire 10 day marathon, a bulk of the content revolving around like fundamentally torturing this guy,
well then it seems like they've got the green light to keep doing it and they made a lot of money
doing it too. And I already know the defense that a lot of people will use here about kick has grown
a lot. So there's a lot of buns in the oven. They can't keep track of every stream every single
every single time. And I recognize that to a certain extent, but this was a big stream for them.
Like this is something that I think would have been on their radar in some capacity and given
kicks history of just letting like really degenerate and illegal shit fly for a while. I think there's
a chance they knew about this, but just were letting it ride because it was a big stream. And they
don't want to be viewed as the platform that's like weenie hut junior or like ban people willy
nilly, which again I get, but when it comes to like torture and illegal shit, there is nothing
wrong with stepping in and banning those accounts. In fact, I would argue it's very beneficial for
your platform to do that. So that way the perception of kick as a whole isn't like a lawless wasteland
where criminals go to broadcast illegal shit. And it seems like the user base would like kick to do
more in cases like this. Aiden Ross made a statement where he mentioned that him and Drake are going
to be covering the funeral costs for Rafael Graven, which I think is a very nice gesture. And from what
I can tell, it seems like Aiden agrees that kick needs to do more in cases like this to stop the
illegal content from being broadcast on that platform. It seems like it's something the users agree
needs to have more action taken on like stopping illegal broadcast of crime on kick. Now to go back
to the actual individuals involved in the abuse of Parminov, one of the lawyers for them has come
forward and said that the victim had cardiovascular problems and that the violence in the videos was
acted. All of those scenes are just staged. They follow a script, he said. Actually going back to the
classic, it's all just acting. A pretty interesting defense tactic here. I wonder if the text message
Rafael Graven sent to his mother agrees that it was all a script and that it was just acting.
And he must have been part of it. It was one hell of a script here. This is up there with some of
Nolan's best scripts. This is crazy to claim that the violence was staged and just acted.
No, the fuck it was not. You can watch it yourself and see that it's not the case. They're trying to
pull that meme of Patrick Stewart going to sleep and then saying wasn't sleeping just acting.
And use it to try and excuse the hand that their clients may have had in the death of a 46-year-old
innocent man on stream. It's, again, you can watch the clips yourself. It's pretty infuriating.
It's hard to watch, but you can. And it's very clear this was not some script and that this was not
just acting. This is real terror and real abuse that this man suffered at the hands of people he
thought were his friends. Now, I do know that there are a couple of clips where Rafael Graven was
playing along with it to a certain degree where he would kind of lean into the humiliation
slash abuse for the sake of the stream. There are a couple moments of that, but it's very rare.
The majority of it is them just lashing out and attacking him or making him do things against
his will and it's not scripted. Very clearly not scripted or fully agreed upon. So it's, I think
that is a very weak defense. I guess we'll see if the French courts agree, but I really think you
can say with high confidence that this stream and these streamers did play a role in what ultimately
happened to Rafael Graven. They may not have directly killed him or anything like that, but I do
think everything they put him through for such an extended period of time had a real role to play
in what happened. It's sickening. This stream was hard to watch the clips from. It was brutal.
Anyway, I just, I had to talk about it a little bit. It's just so fucking crazy. It's really about
it. See ya.